It looks just like snow.
Awesome!
The cherry blossoms this year will be wilting soon.
What?
Tomorrow is a holiday,
so let's go flower-viewing together.
What?
Sounds like fun.
Should I make lunch boxes?
OK.
I'll help too.
Hey, hey.
That's nice.
Yay~!
Hey.
Oh, I'm sorry for deciding so suddenly.
It's fine.
We have nothing to do tomorrow, either.
What should I bring?
Thanks a lot.
Kouki is always causing trouble for you.
I see.
Sorry about that.
Kouki! Rin-chan!
Let's meet at the park tomorrow at 8 AM.
Sure.
That's too early.
How about 9 AM then?
Flower viewing only begins around lunch time.
What?
What about 10 AM...
But I have to watch Gransazers...
I guess it has to be in the afternoon then.
Osu News
Daikichi!
Where's the pail, Daikichi?
It should be under the sink.
Ah, right.
It might rain tomorrow.
Really?
It's called a Spring Storm.
A storm...
It's already raining.
This is bad.
It's raining rather heavily too.
Let's make teruterubozu.
Daikichi!
The rain stopped.
We did it.
The teruterubozu saved us.
I hope they didn't fall off.
It's the smell of leaves.
What?
All the blossoms are gone!
Hey~!
Kouki-kun!
Daikichi!
It's a full bloom in the sky.
「Full Bloom in the Sky」